[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer of 2007"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", ":", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", ":", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", ":", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "What do you think has gone wrong with the American business model, and how can they fix it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "Well, it's very clear that the crisis that erupted in the United States, the financial crisis, three years ago, specifically in the summer of 2007 -- that's where the whole thing began -- showed that capitalism was -- went out of control.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"]}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ":", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "I mean do you think it's time they went back to designing, creating, and building things that they can sell to the world exactly as Apple is doing so successfully?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VBG", ",", "VBG", ",", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Well, clearly Apple is a role model of the American innovation whereby it produced all these products -- iPod, iPhone, iPad -- that are really now dominating all the technology arena in the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "EX", ",", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Are you concerned at all about the succession plans at Apple given the ongoing situation involving Steve Jobs' health?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Well, clearly, as we have read recently in the board of directors over there, has begun looking and talking about succession.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"], "PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["News Corp"]}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "JJ", ":", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "Are you happy with the way things are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Well, you know, News Corp is the only real media global -- that has a global presence that's involved in TV production, in movies, in publishing, in newspapers, digital media, et cetera.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Rupert", "Mr. James"]}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Does James and Rupert both retain your full support?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "I went public by supporting Mr. Rupert and Mr. James after the hearings because I know them very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Rupert"], "PERSON": ["James"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "What did you make of it from Saudi Arabia?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Well, it's very clear that the Arab population is rising because they'd like to have a say in the running of their affairs, running of their government, and this is very legitimate.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Saudi Arabia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Saudi Arabia"]}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "How would you say the mood is in Saudi Arabia about what's going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Thanks god Saudi Arabia is very stable.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Saudi Arabia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Saudi Arabia"]}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Are you pushing your colleagues there in government to be as progressive as you've just been sounding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "I don't agree I'm a lonely voice because all what I tell you right now, my friend Piers, I say that in public in Saudi Arabia, and the majority of Saudis are with me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "In terms of Saudi's role with terrorism and with al Qaeda, do you think that Saudi should be harder and tougher against Islamic fundamentalism than it has been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, you know, I'm a member of the royal family but not a member of the government.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Saudi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Do you think it's time that he just stood down now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Well, I think that Colonel Gadhafi's days are really numbered.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charles", "Diana"], "LOCATION": ["United Kingdom"]}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Now what do you make of them as a couple and the impact they're now having globally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Well, I think, you know, royalty in the UK is very popular, not only in United Kingdom but all the world, and I think that what's happening between the new couple is really a replica, a duplication what happened between Prince Charles and the late Princess Diana.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Where are we as things stand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Well, I think it's clear that we don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Would you both concur that that is where we are now in terms of public opinion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "It depends on whether you -- how you raise revenue, I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "I mean are we now in a position with the American economy where thinking the unthinkable has to be the way to go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "What I think we have to do is we have to reform our tax code in a way that promotes economic growth and not just add tax increases on it to meet a certain number in the budget to say we got a deal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "The fact you've come together and you've put a proposal together which seems to have been the catalyst for what may well be a deal on this, is this a way of both parties saying, OK, things did get a bit out of hand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "I hope so.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["OK"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Where are we going here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Frank, come on, which of all these myriad of roles that you've had have you most enjoyed, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WDT", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "This one's so new, I can't weigh in on it yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "What's not to love, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "The women wouldn't have done so much for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "Do you like that kind of freedom, where you can literally choose anything that rocks your boat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "RUNI: You know, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "How is that kind of column going down generally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "You know, I get -- where the world has changed so much, I get amazingly lovely e-mails from readers when I write about that topic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "America's status as the sole super power is in real peril, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "What's the answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Well part of the answer is an end to the kind of polarized politics and bickering that we have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "How much do you blame the American public for being reckless with their own spending?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "We've all been reckless.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Is President Obama lacking leadership, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "I think he's trying very hard to lead right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harry Potter"]}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Why is the world so obsessed with Harry Potter, if you and I, two reasonably intelligent individuals, have this completely passing us by?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", ",", "CD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "You know, we're the two individuals who can't answer that because we haven't read or watched Harry Potter.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harry Potter"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "What was your take on it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "You know, I tuned into it kind of late.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Is that what you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "To me, when I watch her, her degree of hyperbole and hysteria doesn't feel to me like passion on behalf of victims solely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Do you regret ever getting involved in restaurant critique?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "No, no, it was a fantastic job.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 395, "question": "What was the single best meal you've ever had in a restaurant?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "You know, I get asked that --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Have you eaten there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Or did it get quenched by al this gorging over the years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "I would love to say that the five and half years as restaurant critic put me off food and now I have to force myself to eat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Has it helped you giving up the restaurant critiques?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Oddly, it has hurt me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Are you mad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Well, no, I still live here in New York and I spend most of my time here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1998", "2002"], "LOCATION": ["Washington", "Rome"]}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "CD", "TO", "CD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Do you feel like it's this terrible thing, like an addiction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "No, it's a whole -- I was in Washington last -- I lived there from 1998 to 2002, before I went to Rome.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "110721pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Do you see a potential winner in a race against President Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "I think any smart better right now would have to say it's going to be Mitt Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}]